Class: Runemage<br>Specialization: Chosen of Ylath<br><br><body_bright>The hero will have +1 Morale as long as any Air Elementals are in his army and the hero will already have 10 Dragonblood Crystals at level 1 for the purpose of summoning them (more Crystals can be gained from perks in Shatter Magic and Summoning Magic). This specialization doesn't work if the hero is hired by another faction.<br><color_default>Starts with Basic Summoning Magic.