Headmaster of one of the most prestigious Academies of magic of Al-Safir, Theodorus rarely leaves his precious books and grimoires. Make no mistake though, he is easily one of the best spellcasters of the Silver Cities, and while he's not a young man anymore, his mind is still as calculating as ever. It is rumoured he refused a position at the Circle of Nine because he enjoys teaching more than politics.