There's a certain chance that during a melee attack this creature will use one of the following spells, in addition to inflicting regular damage: Slow, Weakness or Frenzy. (The spell does not work on undead, elemental and mechanical units.) The trigger chance for this ability is 34% if the target stack has double the amount of HP after the hit, 39% if the target stack has the same HP and 52% if the target stack has half the HP. If the hero has Soldier's Luck skill those chances are 57%,63% and 77%.
 