Nicolai is the only child of the Emperor Alexei Griffin and Empress Fiona Unicorn. After his father's death in Sheogh during the War of the Fifth Eclipse, his uncle Godric took over the responsibility to prepare the young prince for his future as the Emperor of the Holy Griffin Empire. Nicolai grew up to be an intelligent and capable emperor, becoming master of warfare, leadership and light magic, beloved by many, and watched over by angels.