Leader of an exploited people, Quroq does not hesitate to use force, guilt, guile, or cruelty to get his way. To him it is a simple matter of efficiency, and no act is considered to be unacceptable in the pursuit of his vision of the Orcish future. Not expecting anything but cruelty from other people, he believes that the only way orcs can retain their freedom is by striking first and striking hard. He usually achieves that feat through hit-and-run tactics that rely heavily on his fast and deadly centaur archers.