Ash got her name during an invasion against Irollan, when she led a charge of a cavalry composed of Nightmares across a patch of the forest for several weeks in a row, moving too fast for the enemies' arrows to reach them. While her kin didn't understand her tactics at first, it quickly became apparent - the forest ended up taking fire from demonic horses' embers, and the elves had no option but retreat, since even rain summoned by druids couldn't quench the infernal flames. After she was done, only ash remained.