This creature always attacks a 4-tile square-shaped area and has a chance to zero the target's Initiative by its blow. It can also demolish walls and towers while besieging towns, dealing 10 damage per creature in the stack. The chance for the initiative reduction is based on the creature's own Hit Points (HP), considering the entire stack. If the target's HP is lower before the hit those odds are equal to 40% + (5% * (HP/TargetHP)). If the target's HP is higher or equal before the hit those odds are equal to 40% - (5% * (TargetHP/HP)).