Class: Nethermage<br>Specialization: Harvester<br><br><body_bright>
A stack of Ghosts joins the hero's army at the start of combat, the amount is equal to 25% of the Ghosts, Spectres and Poltergeists the hero already has in his army. Also, at the start of each week more of such creatures will join the hero's army (provided that some of them are present). The amount is equal to 0.3*hero level. No extra creatures will join before level 2. The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.<br><color_default>Starts with Drain Soul perk.