Class: Runemage<br>Specialization: Rider<br><br><body_bright>At the start of combat the ATB value will be reset for all friendly Bear Riders, Blackbear Riders and Whitebear Riders, causing them to act immediately. All Bear Riders and their upgrades in hero's army also gain +1 to their Attack and Defense for every two levels of the hero, starting on first level.<br><color_default>Starts with Basic Offense.