Class: Death Knight<br>Specialization: Souldrinker<br><br><body_bright>The Suffering spell does not only lower the creature's Attack, but also reduces the target's Defense by an amount equal to Hero Level/3, rounded up. The Defense decrease lasts for the duration of the spell, and is not cumulative. The effect is lost if the spell is replaced by a Curse spell cast by a creature.<br><color_default>Starts with Master of Curses perk.