The hero gains the ability to target an enemy stack with the Mark of the Sorcerer until the end of combat so that each subsequent spell striking that target has its effect doubled and costs twice as much mana.<br><color_default>If there is not enough mana, the effect is not doubled. Moreover, every spell striking another creature will affect this target as well. The caster can be bound to only one target at a time. The caster spends only half a turn to mark a target.