Class: Flamekeeper<br>Specialization: Explosives Expert<br><br><body_bright>The hero summons a minefield immediately at the start of combat and gets to act again after that quickly. The minefield will be placed around the position of the Defenders, Shieldguards or Mountain Guards in the hero's army (ignoring stacks of one unit). The hero's atb value resets to a random value between 0.8 and 0.9 after summoning the minefield, but the Swift Mind perk has no effect on this hero.<br><color_default>Starts with Basic Summoning Magic.