Class: Druid<br>Specialization: Master of the Elements<br><br><body_bright>A stack of Air Elementals joins the hero's army at the start of combat, the amount is equal to 1 + (sqrt(M) * M/200), in which M = the hero's maximum mana. The elementals will be Fire Elementals if the hero is defending (the hero didn't initiate the battle). Additionally, the Summon Elementals and Summon Phoenix spells casted by the hero are more powerful. Effective Spellpower is increased by hero level/4.<br><color_default>Starts with Master of Conjuration perk.