Aislinn has an uncommon connection to the earth. Any time she becomes separated from it, she begins to feel uncomfortable - which is why she brings a bag of fresh soil with her everywhere she goes. Aislinn believes the worms and decay within the dirt actually talk to her. While some think she is delusional, she does have an exceptional amount of control over insects, and a few fellow necromancers believe she actually has somehow developped a druidic connection to Nature.