Warchief of the Whitespear clan from Redskull Island, Kraal proudly traces his lineage back to the first Orc tribes who rebelled against heir Wizard creators and have wandered Ashan, rootless, ever since. A wily, tenacious leader, Kraal is unshakable in his belief that, as Father Sky has decreed, his clan is entitled to the harsh, mountainous lands where they currently reside – lands that form part of the Griffin Duchy. Caught in the middle of bitter enmities that exist between House Griffin and House Wolf, Kraal has studied the human warfare for a long time, and borrowed the best part of it - war machines. Having learned their lesson the hard way, the Wolf Duchy commanders now prefer sending their troops the long way rather than have them wander too close to the Whitespear clan walls.