Infantry Commander: All Footmen, Squires and Vindicators in the hero's army have increased Attack and Defense by 0.5 × HeroLevel. 
 
 Also at the start of each week more swordsman will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). 
<color_default>The amount is 3% × HeroLevel of creature growth rounded down. The amount is boosted by 40% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.
