Class: Renegade<br>Specialization: Infantry Commander<br><br><body_bright>At the start of combat, a stack of friendly Footman, Squires or Vindicators will use the Dash ability, doubling their initiative for 3 turns (the stack must be larger than one unit). All Footmen and upgrades in the hero's army also gain +1 to their Attack and Defense for every two levels of the hero, starting on the first level.<br><color_default>Starts with Basic Combat.