Class: Death Knight<br>Specialization: Grim Reaper<br><br><body_bright>The hero recovers 100 movement points after every battle and at the start of each week additional Wights, Wraiths and Banshees will be available for recruitment in all owned Necropolis towns. The amount is equal to 0.08*hero level. There are no extra creatures available before level 7.<br><color_default>Starts with Basic Combat.