This creature can leap on any enemy target, at great distance, getting a 10 % attack bonus for every tile it goes over. After the leap, the demon lands on the tile next to the target, and is exposed to retaliation 20% more powerfull + 10&% more for every cell it leaps (additive). The leap can't be longer than twice the Grunt's normal movement range ( 8 tiles ), and it can't be shorter than three tiles (activated ability).