Class: Shaman<br>Specialization: Daughter of Light<br><br><body_bright>The hero starts with Light Magic and Father Sky grants the shaman new light magic and adventure spells spontaneously after levelups. The ability to gain new spells follows random patterns but is not based on chance (by lvl 30 you will have gained all Light Magic spells). The Hall of Trial is not needed to learn the spells.<br><color_default>Starts with First Aid Tent perk.