Class: Overlord
Specialization: Lizard Breeder

<body_bright>The Lizard Bite ability deals more damage, depending on hero level. The damage is 1.20+0.01×Level times the regular damage (instead of 0.5). 
 
 Also at the start of each week additional Dark Raiders, Grim Raiders or Brisk Raiders will join the heroes army (provided that some of these creatures are present). 
<color_default>The amount is 3% × HeroLevel of creature growth rounded down. The amount is boosted by 40% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero. 
<color=yellow>Starts with Offence.