Emilia had a simple upbringing as the only daughter of a glassblower employed by an alchemist, yet during her early adulthood a latent affinity for conjuration manifested itself and led to incident involving strange birds suddenly appearing in her master's shop. Excused from her job, and with only a few economies in her pockets, she set out to look for apprenticeship with the Seven Cities wizards. Usually an adult would struggle to find a master since children are known for their faster learning abilities, and most wizards would avoid going through the trouble of schooling an adult from the start, but she got lucky and her talent got noticed by a renowned mage. He offered to school her despite her meager funds, requesting as the only payback to remain at his service after the end of her apprenticeship, which she gladly accepted. Now her apprenticeship years are long gone, and, true to her word, she keeps regularly accomplishing tasks for her old mentor, no matter how strange or dangerous they are.