This creature has a chance of crippling enemies with every attack, decreasing the target’s Speed (-30%) and Initiative (-10%). The chance is based on the creature's own Hit Points (HP), considering the entire stack. If the target's HP is lower after the hit those odds are equal to 40% + (5% * (HP/TargetHP)). If the target's HP is higher or equal after the hit those odds are equal to 40% - (5% * (TargetHP/HP)).