This creature can deal damage on all living enemy stacks within the range of 3 tiles from it. The damage amount depends on the particular enemy's Morale and its distance from the creature (activated ability). The Damage is equal to (12-target morale)×2×The amount of Banshees. Targets adjacent to the Banshees suffer the full damage, while targets one tile further suffer half of it and targets 2 tiles further only 25% of it.