Uland is the heir to the Stoneblaze, one of the most influential families of the Deepflame clan. His ancestors are told to be the first dwarves to have received the blessing of Arkath and the aid of his children, the majestic fire dragons, and today the Stoneblaze continue to entertain a special relationship with them, as protectors, nurturers, and mediators. As the next in the line of succession for the role of the family's patriarch, a lot is expected from Uland. He is often sent by his clan on perilous quests to prove his worth or die trying, yet, so far, his sharp wit and his mastery of magic allowed him to triumph against any challenge. 