Born into nobility, and raised to be both a charismatic leader and proficient with all the weapons in the elven arsenal, Jenova was always well-loved and respected among the elves, but there was a deep dissatisfaction brewing up inside her - she felt that her life was empty and devoid of purpose. During her late adolescence though, fate struck when she uncovered a ploy by some local officials to steal dragon eggs from a close nest and cater them to the Seven Cities to secure some political alliance. Not only saving the eggs brought her the gratitude of the dragons, but she also felt some kind of connection to the proud creatures, and she vowed to serve and protect them from the greed and envy of the ignorant.