Goblin King: At the start of combat additional mana will become available to all friendly Goblin Witch-Doctors (+20) and all Goblins and Goblin Trappers will get to act immediately. Furthermore, at the start of each week more of such creatures will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 1.6*hero level. The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.