Maahir is not unique among Mages for the intensity with which he studies however he is quite unique in the way does it. A seasoned traveler by anyone's standards, Maahir forces his body through endless hardships in the belief that exceptional mental endurance goes hand in hand with exceptional physical endurance. Whether or not it proves to be true remains to be seen, but travelling across Ashan has certainly given him an especially rich perspective on the events that unfold around him.