Lord of the Mountains: At the start of combat the hero casts Righteous Might on a friendly stack of Thanes, Flame Lords or Thunder Thanes (ignoring stacks of one unit). The spell costs no mana and the hero's ATB value is reset to a random value between 0.8 and 0.9, but the Swift Mind perk has no effect on this hero. Furthermore, at the start of each week more of such creatures will be available for recruitment in all owned Fortress towns. The amount is equal to 0.08*hero level. There are no extra creatures available before level 7.