During the War of the Grey Alliance, Nathir was taken prisoner by the demons. Enslaved in their sulfur mines, the hardships he survived unlocked something in him, a power to channel all his anger and his pain into a raw force of destruction no other mage could master. This newfound power allowed him to start a massive prison uprising and escape. He ended up being one of the only three survivors of that rebellion, and he managed to make his way across the fiery wastes of Sheogh and finally back to the Silver Cities. Years after his imprisonment, everybody knows not to mention those events in his presence, for they have marked him far beyond the physical scars he hides behind his mask.