The barbarian Crag Hack was born under another name in the Free City of Eridan Crossing, on the border between the Stag Duchy and the Elven kingdom of Irollan, around 512 YSD. When he was 15, Crag enrolled in a company of mercenaries and participated in many small territorial conflicts in the Empire and the Free Cites. There were several Orcs amount the mercenaries, and Crag soon befriended them, finding the frank, direct ways of the Orcs to his liking. Crag soon became famous for his fearlessness and ferocity in battle, and imperial soldiers started to brand him as a barbarian, more Orc than man. This was meant as an insult, but proved good for the sellsword business. In 548 YSH, at the end of the Elven War, the Orcs decided to journey south and join their brethren in the Pao Islands. They invited Crag to accompany them on their voyage. Having no family left and no war to wage in the Holy Empire, Crag accepted the offer.