Harkenraz has always known how to impose himself in the political scene of Sheogh - when to make a show of force and when to give a rousing speech. While he is aware that he is in no position to dispute the claim of Kha-Beleth on Sheogh, he also knows that nothing is eternal and bids his time while building up influence with the most powerful demons, awaiting the inevitable demise of the Sovereign.