This creature shoots charmed arrows: in addition to normal damage, there's a chance they stun the enemy and delay their turn by 0.2 ATB value. The chance is based on the creature's own Hit Points (HP), considering the entire stack. If the target's HP is lower before the hit those odds are equal to 40% + (5% * (HP/TargetHP)). If the target's HP is higher or equal before the hit those odds are equal to 40% - (5% * (TargetHP/HP)).