Gurvilin is an what you could call an eccentric artist, who, to make matters worse, is also incidentally a wizard. Over the years he has exercised the art of scuplture in the Seven Cities, he has become widely known for his expressive living statues, his incredible abstract art installations, his colorful fireworks, and his tendency to create gargoyles with faces mimicking those of actual personalities in the least flattering ways. As war approached, surprisingly enough he volunteered to offer his services to refill the ever-decreasing ranks of military-grade gargoyles. Little did anybody suspect that it was only an intricate plan to send countless gargoyles in the effigy of Cyrus to the front lines, with little fear of repercussions for Gurvilin knew that he would become an irreplaceable asset for the army in a matter of weeks.