Mukha was born a free Orc in the Eastern Steppes of Ranaar and grew to become a renowned shaman, respected by Orcs and Centaurs. One day, a group of Orc refugees from the Pao Islands arrived in her village and recounted the tale of how they had been attacked, and their children sold into slavery. Mukha was enraged by this ignominy and vowed to Father Sky that no Orc would wear chains while she had breath in her lungs. She set out to the south immediately with a small army, in search of her destiny. Alas, Mukha’s motivated and courageous horde was ambushed by the Duke of Wolf when she crossed the mountains, and all were either captured or killed. Sent to work in the mines, Muhka managed to escape in extravagant fashion. She killed seven guards with a single spell and rode away on the back of a Centaur. Now a permanent resident of the Pao Islands, a rebel with a cause, she has become an inspiration to all Orcs with dreams of freedom.