Class: Conjurer<br>Specialization: Grand Vizier<br><br><body_bright>At the start of combat the hero casts Vampirism on a friendly stack of Djinns, Djinn Sultans or Djinn Viziers (ignoring stacks of one unit). The spell costs no mana and the hero's ATB value is reset to a random value between 0.7 and 0.8 after casting the spell, but the Swift Mind perk has no effect on this hero.<br><color_default>Starts with Basic Dark Magic.