Necromancers can raise dead enemy creatures as own soldiers, using a special resource called Dark Energy. This energy is shared by all Necromancers and gets filled up at the beginning of the week. The amount of energy depends on the total number of Necromancers and their level.<br><body_bright>Move icons of the creatures you want to raise from the top row to your army below. Note that once you raise any creatures by moving their icon to your army, you will not be able to cancel the action.