Rigorously trained but coming from a poor noble family in a backwater of the Griffin Empire, Klaus might have remained unknown if luck had not smiled upon him. Thrust into the most difficult level of a jousting tournament through a simple accident of misfiled parchment, he stunned the crowds by unseating some of the greatest names of the Empire. Since that day, his feats have earned him the devotion of all mounted warriors.