Calh knows when to abandon a sinking ship, and the lack of success in the recent military campaigns of demons have led him to believe that they will not be successful at conquering Ashan anytime soon. So this opportunistic commander decided that instead of waging open war upon Ashan, he would have a better chance of finding a way to anchor demons outside of Sheogh by establishing a small outpost on Ashan far from the populated areas and try a more discreet approach with locals, preferring small raids or even mercenary service to widescale conflict in the name of Kha-Beleth. While his investigations have yet to bear fruit, the tricky nature of his plan has attracted numerous imps to his service, curious to explore the surface and cause various degrees of mischief.