This creature's ranged attack ignores 25% of the target's Defense and has an extra chance to thrust the target back one tile and stun it. The chance for the 'thrust and stun' is based on the creature's own Hit Points (HP), considering the entire stack. If the target's HP is lower before the hit those odds are equal to 40% + (5% * (HP/TargetHP)). If the target's HP is higher or equal before the hit those odds are equal to 40% - (5% * (TargetHP/HP)).