If all the hero's troops have died in combat, an Angel will appear and cast a resurrection spell on the most powerful stack of dead creatures.<br><color_default>The resurrected Hit Points are equal to 240 + 30*(Hero Level). Unlike the normal Resurrection spell however, all creatures except the 4 Elementals can be resurrected by the angel. If the resurrected stack is the last killed stack, it keeps its ATB value and retaliates if retaliation was due. Any active effect is lost.