The tame white owl, Trolinga, who slumbers peacefully on Erling's shoulder, was with him when Erling returned from an extended winter trapping expedition. Questions about it meet only with a secretive smile. As well as the owl, Erling returned from that journey with a profound knowledge of fire magic, and many Dwarves wonder just exactly where he went that winter, and who he met. Since then Erling has acted as a mentor for other dwarves willing to deepen their understanding of the magic of Arkath, and a lot of rune priests have studied under him, and are more than willing to lend him a hand in time of need.