The hero gains +1 Spellpower for every 6 levels and will inflict 30% of normal spell damage against otherwise resistant creatures.<br><color_default>The irresistable effect works against luck based resistance, magic proof and immunities, but only for damaging spells, mind immunities cannot be overruled. Against 75% magic proof (example), the spell damage will become 25% + (30% of the remaining 75%) = 47.5%.