Haggash is an orc orphan who has been left in front of her tribe's shaman's tent, a fate usually reserved for children born under an especially lucky (or unlucky) star. Her tumultous temper has made it difficult for the shaman to tutor her, but today Haggash has all the skills necessary to be a tribe's shaman on her own, but she isn't eager to settle down with one group. Instead, she often goes from one settlement to another, trying to taste everything each has to offer: the finest meals, the loudest celebrations, and the most thrilling raids. Only by getting a clear idea of every clan she can know for sure that she's making the right decision - and why not have a little fun on the way?