Urghat has been nicknamed both "the Shade" and the "the Wise". A witch from her earlier days, her hexes granted her clan, the Black Claws, an edge in their many battles, but this advantage also made them reckless and their rampage left a lot of enemies in its wake. One day, a vanquished clan brought capitulation presents to the Black Claws, and, thanks to her dark powers, Urghat sensed that the gifts were imbued with poison. She tried to warn her fellow clansmen, but the orcs, inebriated with their victories, brushed her away on the account of her young age. This day almost all of her clan perished, as she fled, traumatized, spiteful, and powerless to prevent the catastrophe. As time passed she ended up seeing this as a lesson: never again she would lend her power to someone who would ignore her advice.