The Catapult gains an extra shot, dealing 3 consecutive shots in a turn. The hero also receives the Ammo Cart's Attack bonuses that are normally awarded to the ranged units in the army.
<color=yellow>PvP: The hero will be able to demolish enemy mines.
<color_default>Demolished mines cannot be captured by human players. It takes 5 days to finish the demolition. If any hero visits the mine in those 5 days, the demolition will be cancelled.