Previously a lively duchess of the Griffin Empire, Ornella's curious flirtation with the Necromancers has resulted in her crossing over to the other side of existence as a vampire by the hand of the High Lord Arantir himself. Rejecting any doubts she may have harbored, she is ready to lead undead armies, prove her worth as a death knight, and discover what powers and limitations her new situation implies.