Archilus used to be a dragon knight of some stature, responsible for keeping watch over dragon graveyards to ensure that nothing comes to disturb those sacred places. As the old age started weakening his body, he became fearful of his own demise, and his resolve slowly crumbled to dust. Like many, he was seduced with the promise of eternal life offered by necromancers, and traded his knowledge of the burial sites of dragons for it.