Class: Ranger<br>Specialization: Blade Master<br><br><body_bright>A stack of Blade Dancers joins the hero's army at the start of combat, the amount is equal to 25% of all Blade Dancers, War Dancers and Wind Dancers the hero has in his army. Also, all Blade Dancers and upgrades in hero's army gain +1 to their Attack and Defence for every two levels of the hero, starting on first level.<br><color_default>Starts with Battle Frenzy perk. 