The hero will raise some fallen undead creatures after every battle from a randomly selected stack, the amount is equal to 7+5*hero level in HP. A living hero will also resurrect a quantity of native Tier2 creatures at no mana cost after every battle.<br><color_default>The amount is equal to 50% + 1%*K of all casualties or alternatively 50 + 5*K of all HP lost (whichever results in more resurrected creatures). K = Knowledge of the hero.