Vladimir reasons that with few exceptions, Undead troops will generally be out-thought and out-maneuvered by their living counterparts. On the other hand, every time enemy losses are more important than theirs, their numbers grow, and quickly victory becomes inevitable. Therefore, when given the opportunity, he prefers to use the resilient wights as a frightening vanguard to slowly cull any weak and exposed enemy forces, in order to gather an unstoppable mass of weaker undead without risking to lose any of them in the process.