Increases luck of all creatures in hero's army by 1.<br><color_default>Whenever a luck bonus is triggered the creature does x1.66 damage. If luck is negative the creature does x0.6 damage (1.66 x 0.60 = 1). These numbers will result in an average damage boost of the entire army of ~20% if the hero has 3 luck and ~33% if the hero has 5 luck. If the hero has the critical hit perk those numbers will be ~25% and 40%.