Cyrus was destined for greatness, as from an early age he showed the combination of natural talent and intense competitive ambition that leaders often posess. Mercilessly fighting his way to the top by making unexpected alliances, most notably with the Seven Cities djinni, Cyrus became a young and dynamic First of the Circle. Though over time his brilliance faded under the weight of a huge ego and a tendency to avarice, Cyrus remained a mage of impressive power. While young mages might discreetly look for a change of leadership, his older allies remember his days of glory and remain by his side.