Despite her young age, Mephala is a veteran of several wars, and her experience is esteemed in the elven military, leading to her being often placed in key positions. One of the first lessons she has drawn from her previous battles is that a dead fighter is the first sign of a lost battle, and she learnt by the way of trial and error many helpful tactics to cut her losses and keep her soldiers alive until the end.