The hero gains +1 Spellpower for every 7 levels and will inflict 20% of normal spell damage against otherwise resistant creatures.<br><color_default>The irresistable effect works against luck based resistance, magic proof and immunities, but only for damaging spells, mind immunities cannot be overruled. Against 75% magic proof (example), the spell damage will become 25% + (20% of the remaining 75%) = 40%.