Formerly the court astrologer and favorite counselor of the Griffin Queen Fiona, Markal established a strong (but secret) base of Death cultists within the Holy Empire. The religious leaders of the Church of the Light became suspicious of his activities, however, and when Fiona passed away her advisor was excused. Realizing that he will no longer circulate freely among the other kingdoms of Ashan once he receives the Kiss of the Spider Goddess, Markal furthers the goals of Heresh in the Griffin Empire and the surrounding lands through diplomacy and, of course, skullduggery.