Melodia's emotions and temper can be as changing as the ebb and flow of the sea - in fact, she is rumored to have been touched from birth by Shalassa, the elemental dragon of water. While some degree of attunement with nature is expected from elven rangers, she was always been deemed strange even by those standards, laying down for hours under pouring rains, swimming during storms, and murmuring to ponds when she thought nobody listened. And the strangest part is that you could swear the ponds murmured back.