Azar is a descendant of one of the rebellious mages that helped liberate the beastmen from the Seven Cities slavery. While his ancestor was human, he was completely accepted in the tribe, and Azar is probably more orc than he is human, even if his musculature is somewhat less impressive than his peers'. He is not to be underestimated though - not only he can hold his ground against most orcs in direct combat, but he is also a skilled tracker and animal tamer. It is even told that he uses his knowledge of animal tracks to find shortcuts in unknown territories that anybody else would miss.