This creature can create a local thundercloud inflicting air damage equal to 10 * the size of the stack in a 3x3 area for 3 turns. Shooters in the cloud also get a penalty to their ranged attacks equal to the stack size * 2% with a maximum of 40%. The damage is reduced by Lightning protection, and can be resisted. Friendly units are affected as well, even the Storm Titans that created it. Multiple thunderclouds cannot overlap.