Class: Conjurer<br>Specialization: Mystic<br><br><body_bright>The hero will lose less movement points when using the Arcane Ritual ability and also regenerate an extra amount of mana equal to 2*hero level beyond the regular maximum mana cap. The movement cost is reduced by 2 per mana point recovered and also applies to the mana recovered above the cap.<br><color_default>Starts with Arcane Ritual perk.