Undertaker: A stack of Skeletons joins the hero's army at the start of combat, the amount is equal to 25% of the Skeletons, Skeleton Archers and Skeleton Warriors the hero already has in his army. Also, at the start of each week more of such creatures will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 1.3*hero level. The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.