Supports the Elemental Vision skill. Displays elements on your own creatures, which allows to plan attacks inflicting more damage. Creatures with opposite elements deal more damage to the enemy. Tricksters are granted +1 Morale (not cumulative with multiple towns, doesn't require visiting the town).<br><br><color=0099FF>Governance<color_default><br>Grants the Governor of this town a +1 Attack Bonus.