These are the souls of the most holy ascetics-warriors and sages, with their wishes combined with the angel after death. As guardians of morals and glory, Elrath defends his good name in Ashton by removing those who contribute to the fall of his followers. Their magnificent lances held in their palms often tasted the blood of the enemies of Light in the Empire. In the time of peace, the descent of these beings is a rare event, but recent times are seen more and more often, which is interpreted as preparing Elrath his followers for the coming catastrophe.