Grants the hero the ability to tie his or her own spirit to the spirits of any creatures on the battlefield until the end of combat. If the linked creature receives any damage, the hero will gain some Mana, feeding upon those creatures' suffering.<br><color_default>The amount of mana received is equal to (sqrt(damage inflicted+5))/10. Only one creature can be linked at a time. The hero spends only half a turn to choose a target.