The hero receives a special combat ability to drain the souls of fallen creatures to restore Mana. The drained corpses will disappear from the battlefield.<br><color_default>The hero restores an amount of mana equal to sqrt(HP of drained stack)/4. The hero’s maximum Mana cannot be exceeded. If the hero also has the Cultmaster perk, corpses will explode when they are drained. The explosion will be the same as a Fireball spell cast by the hero; effective Spellpower is 1 if the drained stack was not upgraded, and 2 if it was.