Calid comes from a special bloodline of demons who are able to withstand incredible levels of heat, to the point that they are able to move through fire unscathed. While it doesn't allow her to protect any companions who would try to follow her, she was able to explore areas of Sheogh inaccessible to most of her kin. This ability also enabled her, over the course of years, to develop a special bond with fire elementals, whose presence was never a danger to her.