Class: Overlord<br>Specialization: Chosen of Malassa<br><br><body_bright>Every time the hero uses his regular attack the Fireball spell is also cast on the target. The damage of the Fireball is equal to 24*Power, where power is equal to -2.33 + Hero Level/3. Hero's skills (like Master of Fire) are not taken into account. Furthermore, at the start of each week additional Shadow Dragons, Black Dragons and Red Dragons will be available for recruitment in all owned Dungeon towns. The amount is equal to 0.04*hero level. There are no extra creatures available before level 13.<br><color_default>Starts with Basic Combat.