Adventure Skill: After every combat won, Imps will collect a certain amount of Gold and (one random type of) resources, proportional to the hiring costs of all killed enemy creatures. Furthermore, at level 10, two Imps, Familiars or Vermins will join the hero's army every day, provided that the hero has some of these creatures in his army already.<br><color_default>The amount for each resource type is random between 0 and a Max value; Max(Gold) = Cost*0.015, Max(Wood & Ore) = Cost*0.0001, Max(Precious) = Cost*0.00005, where Cost is the hiring cost (in gold) of the killed enemies.