Resurrects a quantity of native Tier2 creatures after combat. The amount is equal to 30 + 10*D of all Hit Points lost. The resurrection requires 6 mana.<color_default> D = Defense of the hero and the amount is rounded down. Undead, mechanical and elemental creatures cannot be resurrected.<br><br><color=red>Medical<br><color_default>This artifact only works if the hero has one of the following perks: Vitality, Pathfinding or First Aid