The hero can learn all level 3 spells from mage guilds regardless of having mastered any magic school. The hero can also learn high level spells from magic schools not supported by the guilds of native towns. A random level 4 spell will be gained at level 15 and a random level 5 spell at level 25, but only if the hero has mastered an unsupported magic school at basic level or higher.<br><color_default>Four spells can be gained if both unsupported schools are mastered. The spells will still be gained if this perk or the unsupported school is obtained at a later level. It is possible the hero learns nothing if it already acquired the random spell elsewhere.