All infernal troops except Devils and their upgrades are granted an ability to gate into the infernal plane to bring reinforcements back to the battlefield. Each stack can gate only once per combat and will spend 75% of its turn doing it. Reinforcements constitute 25% of the gated ones, will get to act almost immediately after they arrive (their ATB bar will be set to 0.75), and will disappear after the end of the combat.