Class: Flamekeeper<br>Specialization: Flame Wielder<br><br><body_bright>Effective Spellpower of the hero is increased when casting Fireball or Empowered Fireball. The increase is equal to hero level/3. The Mage Guild also summons Fire Elementals instead of Air Elementals, but not if the hero wasn't present on the map on day one or hired from a tavern.<br><color_default>Starts with Advanced Destructive Magic.